http://www.integrify.com/privacy-policy/

Toggle navigation
Features Process BuilderForm DesignerCustom Self-Service Service PortalProcess ReportingProcess Integration (API)Product VideoWorkflow Solutions Solutions by IndustrySolutions by DepartmentIntegrify ServicesCustomers Pricing Resources
Get a Demo
Integrify Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for https://www.integrify.com and any subdomains. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website and any subdomains. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site and its subdomains. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contacts from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization.
If you opt-in, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
All personal data you provide will be handled securely and maintained in secure systems that meet required regulations (e.g. GDRP).
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt-out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us here.
See what data we have about you if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately.
Forms/Registration
On some pages of this website, we may ask users to complete a form to make a request or gain access to restricted content. You may be asked to provide personal information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. As previously stated, we are the sole controllers of any data you provide and will never share, rent or sell any personal data to other parties.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. As a rule, cookies will improve your browsing experience. We use this information to establish the number of unique visitors to our website, pages navigated and provide tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the ‘Help’ section of your browser or by taking a look at the www.aboutcookies.org website which offers guidance for all modern browsers.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time, our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Automate Any Business Process
To see how quickly you can begin automating your business processes, request a demonstration or trial of Integrify.
Get a Free Demo
×
COMPANYAbout IntegrifyContactCareers at IntegrifyPrivacy PolicyBlog
20 N. Wacker Dr. #3330Chicago IL 60606
P (888) 536-9629
F (312) 345-9119
support@integrify.com
sales@integrify.com
jobs@integrify.com
PRODUCTVideo ToursCustomersContract Management Process | Manage Contract ApprovalsSalesForce Workflow Re-ImaginedService Request Management Software | IntegrifySoftware Change RequestsOperations Management Software | Business Improvement
RESOURCESGet Help Using IntegrifyBlogWorkflow Examples | See How Workflow Automation Is UsedBusiness Process Automation and Digital TransformationWorkflow Management Software | Manage Work BetterWorkflow Automation | Definition, Examples, and ToolsWorkflow SoftwarePARTNERSOur PartnersPartner ListRequest to Become a Partner
SOCIAL
LATEST POSTSHow To Improve Leadership SkillsHow To Stay Positive At WorkArticle Roundup: Unplugging for the HolidaysHow To Improve Your Writing At Work
Copyright © 2020 Integrify All rights reserved.
